Baltimore Baltimore Baltimore Baltimore Merlin y'all are one of a kind for for real one of a
kind thank you Baltimore for showing up and showing out tonight I really played myself
no I didn't that's not actually accurate because more importantly I want to thank I want to shout
out Derek Adams and his space the Charm City Cultural Cultivation Headquarters for welcoming
us in to do tonight's event for all of y'all who came not knowing if your RSVP was going to be
honored and just coming on a hope and a prayer I truly appreciate you there was a whole mess up
mishap with the with the email system you know I always tell y'all I'm a very small staff it's me
and one other person so you know we were trying to trying our best and this time it kind of didn't
pan out as perfect as we would have liked it to nonetheless I want to thank all of you all who
came through and were so patient and so understanding um and we had just such a beautiful time
like for real we had such a beautiful time thank you Miss Debbie for coming through always showing
love and um someone in here said Baltimore is a very dangerous city and the people are not friendly
well that was not my experience and that's actually never been my experience in Baltimore the last time
I was in Baltimore was to do five shows and to do five stand-up comedy shows and I literally sold out
all five of them so I'm not really sure what you're talking about um every time I come to Baltimore I'm
actually shown a lot of love and I think when people make statements like that they're nine
times out of ten basing them on like one or two experiences actually the only two people who were
disrespectful to me tonight were white people in Baltimore one was the uber driver who pulled up
and promptly canceled when he saw me and brother Amir standing outside and two was the white lady who by
the end of the meet and greet was disappointed that I did not give her time to pour upon praise
pour praises upon me even though it was very clear that we were under a time crunch because the venue's
workers you know had had reached the end of their evening and so she got um she got a reading and it
wasn't from the book then she came back and then was like you know I was just sorry because I'm really
disappointed and I'm just always amazed and I was like you know it's always white women
why are you centering yourself why are you giving me emotional labor and I just want to shout out my
empaths because people really don't know how much emotional labor we do let me tell you people do not
understand how much emotional labor empaths do we are reading the room we are doing the um
Jada get the fuck off my life I really don't want to go live with you actually get off my life
I don't I live in Baltimore and I have first-hand experience you only saw the tourist side of
Baltimore what how is that useful right now so the amount of energy that it takes as a empath in a room
is a lot you know and I'm not complaining by any means because my empathy is a super my empathicness
is a superpower however it really is something that maybe those who aren't empaths should know about
like I'm literally I'm doing lifting because I'm also reading other people's stuff that they may not
even know how to read so I'm doing the math I'm doing the emotional math for them I am making space
I am being considerate of folks emotional limitations like all of that is happening
and I'm doing that on front street right and um when I am doing a signing it's also a whole other
thing because I really try my best to give each person the energy I try to get I try to give every
single person the energy there's also just something very real about the fact that it's
the end of the night and we're trying to get everybody in trying to get everybody their their
bit of energy and I think that there's something to be said for just having the consciousness that
it's not just you and yes you may have waited in line and yes you deserve your time but that
doesn't mean you're gonna get it and I think that's something that as adults we have to really
understand just because you deserve something doesn't mean you're gonna get it new white lady
really started crying this white lady started crying because she said she was disappointed that
when she came to talk to me she didn't get to finish her full statement before she was asked to
take a picture y'all I was trying something like 150 books and everybody else there was so beautiful
and and making friends in Lyme and I'm so appreciative of the mothers who well not just the mothers but
the parents who be bringing their kids and sometimes it's their teens sometimes it they bring their
neurodivergent kids and I feel so honored that they feel safe to bring those folks into the space with
me it happens all the time and I'm every time just so honored and um and I make it I try my best to
make even more time for the kids right so a new white lady go stand in the center of the room y'all
and say I'm disappointed oh my god somebody got it on tape
somebody got it on tape and you know what anybody else was quiet so no I did not laugh and walk away
because that shit is unacceptable and it's really disrespectful to even be doing that so no it's
not a laugh and walk away and that's what we we get taught that that's like the way to deal with
things but what it does a lot of times is it gives people license to think that shit is acceptable
no get that shit the fuck out of here I'm in here signing all of these damn books trying to give all
of these people the energy and the the the attention I'm also trying to be conscious of the fact that there
are people here working the event that they have welcomed me into that space and that I need to be
acknowledging of the fact that they have a time limit of when they're going to get out of work
and I should not be just overstepping that and I'm also being conscious of the fact that I have
volunteers here in the same capacity and the reality is that I'm also tired as fuck I did a four hour show
today I did a four hour show I woke up at 7 a.m. I wrote views from Amanda Land then I did views from
Amanda Land then I went and helped um draw out uh draw out banners for an action then I went to
Baltimore thank you Nick then she gonna come back then she gonna come back and be like well no I want
to apologize but really I just was really disappointed bitch I don't so big up to the rest of y'all
who made the space so fertile who made the space so fertile with it just felt like it was like
like we were engaging each other thank you AGO like I tried to sign the books with the messages
we're done I didn't get to eat nothing this is my dinner because I'm not on TikTok I have an account
but I don't do shit on TikTok fuck TikTok so and the people at the space when I got there I saw they
had turntables and so I got to DJ which I have not done in a long time so I got to DJ and that felt so
good and that that set the tone and then I had the whole room sing do what that thing when we were
I don't want to expand my team I don't want to expand my team I don't want to expand my growth I don't
want to do none of that shit this is what y'all don't understand all of that expansion and growth
and blah blah blah that's capitalist mindset all that is capitalism all of it expand expand scale scale
somebody in here talking some real idiotic shit and y'all gonna need to get her together before I get
her out of here okay so I got a couple people I got a block Jesus I haven't read enough marks and
angles to have a favorite work I am back thank you Eric he's like y'all gotta do everything word um
my really good friend from college rara robert hardy he came I did not know he was coming through
it was so good to see him and to see how healthy he is mentally physically emotionally all the above
because that that's my nigga nigga okay and it was really like he sat next to me while I did the talk
he has a one-woman show that's going down in Baltimore I think on January 3rd
so um his name is rara his name is Robert Hardy also known as rara we went to purchase together
in the acting conservatory y'all trying to get me to talk about fanon at 11 30 like can I please just
talk about what I'm talking about please can you just listen
like so it's always dope when those moments happen where it's like a it's like both in the room like
people who are just kind of coming to you but then also people who have been with you you know and
I'm on a journey where I get to um where I'm getting to expand my like I may not be expanding my
business but I'm expanding I may not be expanding my business but I'm expanding my mind I'm expanding
my understanding and so it's really cool to get to to do that in um in these spaces and you all make
these spaces such safe spaces um and I think it's really dope how much you all also protect the space
like don't that's not lost on me that the the folks that come to these talks they are so supportive of
the people who are asking questions you know they are so encouraging of people asking questions
they're very uh tapped into the conversations and the exchanges and that is what allows for us to
continue to grow and then when I get to see y'all in the line talking and and carrying on you know uh
like taking parts of the conversation and having your own like your own exchanges about that like
it really you know we we had a number of we had a number done on us in um in COVID you know where we
were so disconnected from each other so we're still getting back into the mix and as we continue
to be under surveillance of such a severe measure and as we continue to see the Zionism expand
and suppress and repress which it absolutely is going to do everything that you have seen them
do in Palestine they're about to do here everything you've seen them do in Lebanon they're about to do
here remember I said it and understand that you are going to be forced to find another way of
existing and community and you're going to be forced to dis to unlearn right and so that's the work
that we do uh on our own but also in these in these in these exchanges so just know that I really
appreciate y'all um rays of light said I appreciate your grounding technique for your anxiety attack
today so yeah when I have an anxiety attack I know that I either need to go to if I don't if I don't do
a grounding technique it's gonna make me go to sleep so if I if I have an anxiety attack I know
that I typically just need to lay down so earlier today on views from amanda land I had to lay down
so literally if you watch the episode on youtube amanda seal tv you will see me lay down
in the middle of the interview
and uh thank you uni party I love me some brianna and sabby I think they are just so brilliant and I
learn so much anytime I'm around them I have um I had lunch with with brianna and some other folks
yesterday hazami and um eugene per year and I like I'm not even talking I'm not even asking questions
I'm not even asking questions I'm like what what y'all talking about who is this what's that explain
you know like I know some of y'all think some people be like oh amanda don't want to
she thinks she's the smartest in the room no I don't I know I'm the only amanda in the room
I'll tell you that but I keep folks around me that know shit I don't know
mm-hmm and I know shit they don't know and I think different than them thank you miss debbie
yeah I had me a little anxiety attack earlier and it's not that k key I got a little mouth
so I always want to extend my appreciation to baltimore and dc because y'all really show me so
much love like there's three cities where I feel like outside of new york but where I feel like
I don't ever have to do extra labor philly baltimore dc
like everything everything I'm saying gets to gets across I don't ever feel like I got a
extra explain and that's no shade to anywhere else it's not but it is cool
to have these places where we know what it is you know and no it's not R.I.P. Chicago
and it's not but the midwest is a different dance listen I've been around this entire nation
three times and so I know that I have to adjust in certain spaces and all I'm saying is that I
don't have to adjust at all in those cities I just left the west coast Leah I was in San Diego LA
I was in Seattle so I got to make my way back there so I can go to Portland I'd like to go to
Sacramento in the Bay Area start through Phoenix you know so no you don't have to apologize so next
week I'm in the south I'm in New Orleans on the 11th in order for me to come to Hawaii I need to be
invited by Hawaiians that's the kicker the only way I will come to Hawaii is if I am invited by
Hawaiians because I'm not trying to disrespect their work their efforts at being in control of their
island being of their of their country so if Hawaiians are like we would like you to come
so be it so be it um so next week I'm in Houston on the 10th I'm in New Orleans on the 11th I am in
Atlanta on the 13th and I'm in Dallas on the 14th and that'll be it for this year and next year
I will do my best to make sure that I get to Philly get to Newark I know you see them shred
shreds melanin right I'm like okay I guess we doing the the views from mandolin roll call
and I want to make it to the south I want to go to Jackson Mississippi I want to go to Birmingham
Alabama um so you know I really would like to eventually get back to Memphis but I didn't get
to go to Memphis when I was supposed to all the information is on my website or will be on my
website oh no it's on my website all the information for all the cities is on my website
I'm about to insert the links right now then I gotta book my travel but let me just do this right now
so Houston edit I know y'all are like well maybe if you have an assistant or somebody like it'll be
more efficient so basically what I decided was that if my life requires an assistant
it's too big I decided that when I left Hollywood and I'm sticking with it I don't want a life that
requires an assistant so take that take that take that I saw somebody smart ass in here say
oh you're too smart to eat Doritos first of all why the fuck can't y'all just shut the hell up
why why is it so difficult for you to act on in on the internet like you would in real life
why would you if you said that to me in real life I would tell you to get the fuck out my face
um I know Miss Leo I didn't make the anti-semitic list this year y'all but congrats to Miss Rachel
congrats to Miss Rachel for making top nine anti-semitics of the year that's an honor
by the by the organization that made it it's an honor no so I gotta make the RSVP link and I hope
I gotta do it right for Dallas no I don't do tv and movies no more I'm not not into it no more tv and
movies for me I'm being called to something else so I gotta do that but anyways I came in here to
thank you guys shout out to Baltimore and I wish all of you a great evening and I hope to see those
of you who can in the south next week